维托:好,西维尔,下一个进门的女孩就是你的.
Vito: OK Seaver, the next chick who walks through that door is yours.
本:嗯,还不太坏.
Ben: Mmmm, not too shabby.
维托:那个有女人味.
Vito: Now that's a woman.
斯汀奇:玛蓉.
Stinky: Marone.
本:嘿,玛丽?米格里安那戴胸罩了吗?假的,加了衬垫.
Ben: Hey, is Mary Migliana wearing falsies? False alarm, training bra.
斯汀奇:她想做什么?
Stinky: What's she training to do, anyway?
本和朋友:闭嘴,斯汀奇!
Ben and Friend: Shut up, Stinky!
本:嘿,看茱迪·琼斯穿的?
Ben: Hey, look at what Jude Jones is wearing.
维托:嘿,西维尔,
Vito: Hey, Seaver, you got no shot at Jude.
你不要盯着茱迪了,除非她会对理着这种傻瓜头的人感兴趣.
Unless she's into guys with dorky haircuts.
本:听着,这不是我的主意.我的爸爸让我理成这样.
Ben: Look, this wasn't my idea. My dad made me get a haircut.
维托:嘿,她走过来了.
Vito: Hey, she's coming over.
茱迪:你好,本,新发型?
Judy: Hi Ben, new haircut?
本:看上去很差劲,是吧?
Ben: Looks pretty bad, doesn't it?
茱迪:不,它看起来很酷.
Judy: No, I think it looks really cool.
斯汀奇:有女孩那样对我,我非揍她不可.本!!
Stinky: Boy, if some girl did that to me, I'd slug her. Ben!!
本:她想要我.
Ben: She wants me.
斯汀奇:为什么?
Stinky: For what?
本:我不知道.
Ben: I don't know.
本:爸爸,爸爸!我要问你件事!!
Ben: Dad, Dad, I gotta ask you something!!
杰森:你好,本,
Jason: Hey, hi Ben.
你的新发型肯定获得了不少赞扬.
Hey, bet ya got a lot of complements on your new haircut, huh?
本:爸爸.我要问你件事.
Ben: Later Dad. Look, I gotta ask you something.
杰森:好的,本,说吧.
Jason: OK Benny, shoot.
本:女孩用手指梳男孩的头发,是什么意思?
Ben: What does it mean when a girl runs her fingers through a guy's hair?
杰森:很好,当一个女孩……对了,
Jason: Well, when a girl... Yep, yep, yep.
我很高兴你来问我,本,
Well I'm glad you came to me on this Ben.
我想我们应该就这个问题作一些补充,如何?
I guess it is time we had a little refresher on that subject, huh?
本:但是我想知道的是……
Ben: But all I wanted to know was...
杰森:好了,坐下来,
Jason: That's alright, go have a seat; we'll start at the beginning.
我们从头开始,我们可以跳过雄蕊,
Na, we can skip the pistols and the stamens with you, can't we Ben, huh?
雌蕊,本?
Yes, let's start with our friends the mammals, hmm?
是的,我们从我们的朋友哺乳动物开始?
Now, as you remember, Ben,
你记住,本,
when that old hump back whale starts to swim with other hump back whales,
当长大的座头鲸开始和家族以外的,年龄相仿的座头鲸一起游泳的时候……
his own age, outside the family unit...
本:爸爸讲了太多我不想知道的事.
Ben: All I'm saying is that Dad told me a lot more than I wanted to
know...ever.
迈克:座头鲸?
Mike: The hump back whale deal?
本:我只是想问,
Ben: I mean, all I asked was,
一个女孩用手指梳你的头发是什么意思?
what does it mean when a girl runs her fingers through a guy's hair?
迈克:啊,本,本,你为什么问爸爸,不来问我?
Mike: Ah, Benny, Benny, why would you wanna ask Dad that when you've got me?
本:爸爸总是说,去找他,"
Ben: Well, Dad always says,
别像迈克那样,只是说一些街上的传言".
come to him; "don't just pick it up in the street like Mike did."
迈克:嘿,这儿你能看到街吗?
Mike: Hey, you see a street here?
本:不,但是我只是……
Ben: No. But I was just...
迈克:本,你真应该知道,
Mike: Benny, you've got to understand, women today like guys who are...
如今女人们喜欢的小伙子,得绅士,
who are gentle and sensitive;
体贴,谁能知道得比我更多呢?
and who knows how to fake that slop better than me? Alright?
好了,演示一下她怎么做的?
Now, show me exactly what she did.
本:就像这样.
Ben: She went like this.
迈克:好的,你感觉怎么样?
Mike: Alright, now how'd it make you feel?
本:天哪,我喜欢.
Ben: God help me, I loved it!!
迈克:嗯?
Mike: Yeah?
本:这表示她要我,对吧?
Ben: So it means she wants me, right?
迈克:嗯,不用怀疑.
Mike: Ah, no doubt about it.
本:迈克,我以前认为女孩都是可爱的,
Ben: Mike, I thought girls were cute and stuff before,
但是没有人故意这样碰我.
but I've never had one touch me on purpose and, like, mean it.
迈克:是的,是的,
Mike: Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, ah!!
我永远,永远不会忘记第一个女孩那样对我.
I'll never, never ever forget the first girl that did that to me. Ronda...
隆达,或者是其他名字.
something or other.
本:你不记得她的名字了?
Ben: You don't remember her last name?
迈克:嘿,让我想一下,那是在幼儿园.
Mike: Hey, giver me a break, it was in nursery school.
本:发生在幼儿园?
Ben: This happened to you in nursery school?
迈克:是的,那是午睡时间,
Mike: Oh yeah. It was nap time, as I recall.
我们把塑料布铺在地上,
We had just put the plastic over the clay to...err...keep it moist.
然后我们搭起了小床,感觉有人轻微地拉扯我的衣服.
Then we set up our cots, and I felt this tiny tug on my smock.
本:嘿!你还记得我吗?
Ben: Hey! Remember me?
迈克:哦,好的,
Mike: Oh! Oh! Right, sorry Benny.
对不起,本.好,
OK, now listen, you just got to realize Benny,
现在听着,你刚刚意识到,本,
that this is the first time a girl has ever put a move on you.
这是第一次有女孩向你表示,你准备下一步怎么办呢?
Now, are you ready to take that next step?
本:是的!是的!是的!
Ben: Yes! Yes! Yes!
迈克:好,很好!
Mike: Alright! Good!
本:我可以借你的公寓吗?
Ben: Can I borrow your apartment?
迈克:为什么?
Mike: For what?
本:我不知道.我可以借你的车吗?
Ben: I don't know. Can I borrow your car?
迈克:干什么?
Mike: For what?
本:我不知道!
Ben: I don't know!!
迈克:本,本,
Mike: Benny, Benny, you're skipping some major steps here!!
你跳过了一些重要的步骤!但是,
But, I gotta say, excellent attitude.
我要说态度很棒.你的血管里流的是西维尔家族的血.
Seems you got that Seaver blood pumping through those veins.
本:说吧.
Ben: Tell me about it.
迈克:好的,现在你必须知道她的名字,对吧?
Mike: Yeah. Alright, now you'll have to put a lip-lock on what's her name
alright
本:茱迪,她的名字是茱迪·琼斯.
Ben: Judy. Her name's Judy Jones.
迈克:嘿,下来,好,现在,
Mike: Hey, down boy. Alright, now listen...listen...
听着,听着,我们同意那就是你的目标,对吧?
we agree that is your goal, right?
本:是的,是的!!那是我的目标.谢谢,
Ben: Yeah. Yeah!! That is my goal! Thanks Mike, I'm glad I talked to you!!
迈克.我很高兴和你谈话!我应该怎么做呢?
What do I do?
迈克:你所要做的,就是约她出来.
Mike: All you gotta do, is ask her out.
本:好的,我约她出来,我约她去哪呢?
Ben: Right. I'll ask her out. Where should I ask her to go?
迈克:电影院,那总是一个很好的所在.
Mike: A movie is always the perfect cover.
本:好的.
Ben: Right.
迈克:本,别走.
Mike: Ben, don't move.
本:为什么看电影?
Ben: A movie, why?
迈克:本,因为那里黑啊,
Mike: Because Benny, it's dark, you get to sit real close, and maybe,
你可以挨得近一点,也许,只是也许.
just maybe, she'll share your goobers.
迈克:嘿,记得我喜欢鸡蛋吗?
Mike: Hey, remember how I like my eggs?
开萝尔:记得我怎么讨厌你吗?
Carol: Remember how I hate your guts?
迈克:开萝尔,如果我早知道你在这做早饭的话,我就不会待在屋里吃我的牛肉干了.
Mike: You know Carol, if I knew you were in here making breakfast, I would
have stayed in my room with my beef jerky
开萝尔:我做饭的唯一原因是因为妈妈要去上她的健身课.
Carol: The only reason I'm cooking is because Mom's got to get to her
exercise class.
迈克:好的,好的.
Mike: Yeah, yeah, yeah! Serve it up, wench!
杰森:好的,我会习惯其他人做饭的.
Jason: Well, well, well; someone else cooking, I could get use to this.
迈克:是的,我刚才也是这么说的.
Mike: Yeah, you know, I was just saying the same thing.
麦琪:哦,好,
Maggie: Oh, well, well, well, someone else doing the cooking,
我会习惯其他人做饭的.
I could get use to this.
迈克和杰森:是的,我刚才也是这么说的.
Mike and Jason: Yeah, I was just saying the same thing.
本:开萝尔在做饭?
Ben: Carol's cooking?
迈克:本,别再提了,已经过时了.
Mike: Forget it Ben, it's been covered.
麦琪:嘿,小南瓜,你今天看起来格外的帅.
Maggie: Hey pumpkin, you look extra handsome today.
本:那是我的计划.
Ben: That's my plan.
(婴儿哭泣声)
(baby crying)
杰森:是的,轮到我了.
Jason: Yes, it's my turn.
麦琪:好,我得走了.
Maggie: Well, I...err...have to run.
迈克:好.
Mike: OK.
开萝尔:再见,妈妈.
Carol: See you, Mom.
麦琪:孩子们,我得走了.
Maggie: Boy, do I have to run.
迈克:你用的什么香水?总是奶油糖果味吗?
Mike: So, what's this cologne you're wearing? Forever butterscotch?
本:迈克,你答应的!
Ben: Mike, you promised!
迈克:好吧.我不说,现在你在恋爱中.
Mike: Alright, alright. I won't say a word, now that you're in love.
本:迈克,很好!
Ben: Mike, come on!
开萝尔:恋爱!本,你?
Carol: In love! Ben, you?
本:我得去学校了.
Ben: I gotta get to school.
开萝尔:但是本,你还没吃早饭呢.
Carol: But Ben, you didn't touch your breakfast.
本:我不饿.
Ben: I'm not hungry.
开萝尔:胃口都没了,真的是恋爱.
Carol: Loss of appetite, it's definitely love.
啊,我应该找一个男朋友,这样可以代替节食了.
Ah, I should have just found a guy, instead of going on that diet.
迈克:你怎么找男朋友呢?你看起来像头猪!
Mike: How could you have found a guy? You were a pig!
老师:我不介意.亚历山大?格拉汉姆?贝尔对沃森先生说了什么呢?
Teacher: I don't care. What did Alexander Graham Bell say to Mr. Watson?
维托:嗯……大概是亲爱的沃森.
Vito: Errm...Elementary my dear Watson.
老师:错了,维托,现在让我们听听西维尔先生的答案,
Teacher: Wrong Vito, and now let's hear what Mr.
他已经完全写了出来.不,西维尔先生,
Seaver's answer is; which he has so thoughtfully written down for us.
亚历山大?格拉汉姆?贝尔在电话里对沃森先生说的第一句话不是,"
No, Mr. Seaver, Alexander Graham Bell's first words on the telephone to Mr.
你好,你真可爱,想去看电影吗?"
Watson, were not, "hi, you're cute. Wanna go to a movie?"
斯汀奇:那太危险了,我都快尿裤子了.
Stinky: That was great, I almost wet my pants.
维托:斯汀奇,下次再交好运吧.
Vito: Better luck next time stinky.
本:嘿,你们快走,茱迪来了.
Ben: Hey guys spread out, Judy's coming over.
茱迪:这是寄给我的吗?
Judy: Was this addressed to me?
本:不,不是.你会吗?
Ben: No, not at all. So could you?
茱迪:我会什么?
Judy: Could I what?
本:会和我看电影?
Ben: Go to a movie with me?
茱迪:不,我很抱歉.
Judy: No. I'm sorry.
本:无论如何都要谢谢你.
Ben: Thanks anyway.
茱迪:别这样,不是我不想去,
Judy: No. It's not that I don't want to,
只是我妈说我两年之内不能出去约会.不过,
it's just that my mom says that I can't go out on date dates for another
如果有人要办聚会,
two years. But, if like somebody was having a party, I could meet you there.
我可以在那见你,我喜欢在那见你.
I'd love to meet you there.
本:聚会?好的,太巧了,有人要办聚会!
Ben: Party? Well, son of a gun, somebody is having a party!
茱迪:谁?
Judy: Who?
本:我.
Ben: Me.
茱迪:为什么你刚才不说呢?
Judy: Why didn't you just say so?
本:我刚才也在问我自己.
Ben: I was just asking myself the same question.
茱迪:聚会什么时候?
Judy: When's the party?
本:你今晚有空吗?
Ben: You busy tonight?
茱迪:有空.
Judy: No.
本:那就是今晚,在我家里.
Ben: It's tonight, at my house.
茱迪:什么样的聚会?
Judy: What kind of party?
本:生日聚会.
Ben: A birthday party.
茱迪:谁的生日?
Judy: Whose birthday?
本:我的.
Ben: Mine.
茱迪:我以为你的生日在十月.
Judy: I thought your birthday was in October.
本:很多人都这么以为.
Ben: A lot of people do.
茱迪:我不会错过的,本.
Judy: I wouldn't miss it for the world, Benjamin.
本:喔,维托,
Ben: Benjamin! Wow! Vito, Stinky,
斯汀奇,我刚才请了茱迪今晚去我家参加生日聚会.
I just invited Judy to a birthday party at my house tonight.
维托:但是今天不是你的生日.
Vito: But it's not even your birthday.
本:我不介意.
Ben: I don't care.
朋友们:好的!聚会!聚会!
Friends: Alright! Party! Party!
本:不,维托,我介意.哦,不.
Ben: No, Vito, I do care, don't!!! Oh no.
同学:你,西维尔,我可以带我的表弟霍波肯吗?
Classmate: Yo, Seaver, can I bring my cousin from Hoboken?
杰森:好的,克莉丝,我来给讲一下我们人类的朋友,
Jason: Well Chrissy, let me tell you about our friend the mammal; see yes,
哺乳动物,是的,座头鲸……
there's a hump back whale...
本:迈克在哪?
Ben: Where's Mike?
杰森:嘿嘿,我们还没打招呼呢?
Jason: Hey, hey, don't we even get a hello?
本:你好!迈克在哪儿?
Ben: Hello! Where's Mike?
杰森:本,你看上去很不安.
Jason: Ben, you seem upset.
本:我不是不安,我不需要再听什么座头鲸了.
Ben: I'm not upset, and I don't need to know anymore about hump back whales.
我需要迈克.
I need Mike.
杰森:座头鲸厌倦独自游泳了……
Jason: You see, the hump back whale gets tired of swimming alone...
迈克:本,我必须得竭尽全力,但是,真的,
Mike: Ben, I have got myself into some really doozies, but this is truly,
好大一群人呢.你请了多少?今晚有三十个小伙子要来吗?
major league. OK, so you've got what, thirty kids coming over tonight?
本:如果幸运的话,加起来就有.
Ben: If I'm lucky that will be all.
迈克:喔喔!!这太糟糕了,
Mike: Woo hoo!! This is bad! Well, let's keep our heads here.
我们得好好想想.是的,
Alright, now, you're having a birthday party tonight,
尼今晚要办一个生日聚会,但是今天并不是你的生日,即使是,
but it's not really your birthday; and even if it was,
你也没有得到爸爸妈妈的允许.该怎么办呢?
you don't have Mom and Dad's permission to have a party. Is that about it?
喔,那真得太糟了.
Woo! This is real bad.
本:看来我只能告诉所有人,我撒谎了,这里没有聚会.
Ben: I'll just tell everybody that I lied and there's no party.
迈克:不,不,不,
Mike: No, no, no, Benny, listen to me.
本,听我说,
If your friends cannot rely on your word, especially when you're lying,
如果你的朋友不再相信你,尤其是当你撒谎时,那么你就失去了作为小伙子的未来.
then you've got no future as a teenager.
本:我的错误在于今天不是我的生日吗?
Ben: Is it my fault it's not my birthday?
迈克:嘿,是这样!本,我有办法了.
Mike: Hey, that's it!! That's it Benny, I got it.
本:好的,告诉我!
Ben: Well give it to me!
迈克:今天为什么不能是你的生日?知道我什么意思吗?
Mike: Why can't today be your birthday? Know what I mean?
本:不知道.
Ben: No.
迈克:来,本,你没听我说啊?
Mike: Come on Benny, aren't you listening to me?
本:听什么啊?
Ben: Listening to what?
迈克:我们要为你举办生日聚会.
Mike: We are gonna have your birthday party.
本:但是今天不是我的生日!!!
Ben: But it's not my birthday!!!
迈克:本!本!来,
Mike: Benny! Benny! Come on, wake up and smell your birthday cake.
醒醒,闻一下你的生日蛋糕.我们需要几个人来操办.
We're going to need some brains on this operation.
本:斯汀奇可以帮忙.
Ben: Stinky can help.
迈克:你该被扔出窗子了,
Mike: You are this close to being tossed out of that window.
我说的是开萝尔.
I am talking about Carol.
本:开萝尔不会帮我.
Ben: Carol will never help me.
迈克:哦,来吧,
Mike: Oh come on Ben.
本.你知道,
You know how any time someone mentions romance,
只要有人提到浪漫,开萝尔都会帮忙的.
Carol goes completely bap-loop?
本:真的吗?
Ben: Yeah. So?
迈克:我们对她讲茱迪,她就会眼泪汪汪,
Mike: So we tell her about Judy and she'll get all weepy like mum and
像妈妈一样,然后帮你.我现在几乎能听见她高分贝的尖叫了.
then she'll help out. I can almost hear that high pitched squeal now.
开萝尔:哦!她真的对你有好感吗?
Carol: Ohh! Does she feel the same way about you?
本:我认为是这样.你会帮忙呢?
Ben: I think so. So will ya?
开萝尔:好的,当然我会帮你.哦,本!
Carol: Well of course I'll help you. Oh Ben!
迈克:我说的对吧?
Mike: What did I tell you?
开萝尔:现在我们时间不多了.
Carol: Now we don't have much time here.
迈克:看,本?她正在思考.
Mike: See Bennie? She's already thinking.
开萝尔:我有了一个好办法,让妈妈和爸爸外出.
Carol: I know the perfect way to get mum and dad out of the house.
迈克,我认为你会做到?
Mike I assume you are doing your part to help out?
迈克:你了解我.无论什么代价.
Mike: Ah. You know me. Whatever it takes.
本:为什么迈克还没来电话呢?
Ben: Why hasn't Mike called yet?
开萝尔:他会的,他会的.
Carol: He will, he will.
本:他知道怎么说吗?
Ben: Sure he knows what to say?
开萝尔:放松点,我甚至给他写了份草稿.
Carol: Relax, I even wrote him a script.
杰森:你是对的,宝贝.
Jason: You're right honey. What was I thinking?
我在想什么呢?当然,我要做晚饭,
Of course, I'll cook dinner, you breast feed the baby.
你给宝宝喂奶.你们在做什么呢?
What are you guys doing?
本:等这个见鬼的电话响.
Ben: Waiting for the stinking phone to ring.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
(电话铃声)
(phone rings)
本:那是你的,爸爸.
Ben: It's for you dad.
杰森:你怎么知道?
Jason: How do you know that?
本:我知道,我怎么会知道呢?
Ben: I don't. How could I?
杰森:你好,我是西维尔医生.
Jason: Hello. Yes, this is doctor Seaver.
迈克:(印度人腔调)哦,你好.我有一个非常非常好的消息要告诉你.
Mike: (in Indian accent) Oh hello. I very very wonderful news coming to you.
杰森:你是谁?
Jason: Who is this?
迈克:哦,我叫马迪,
Mike: Oh, Personally I am Madi. Manager of the Star of India restaurant.
印度之星饭店的经理.很高兴通知你,
Pleased to be informing you that tonight only,
在我们简陋的饭店里,你们赢得了一份今晚的双人免费晚餐,
you have won a free dinner for two at my pitiful establishment.
只能是今晚.那会是一次很棒的经历.
That should be beautiful establishment.
杰森:非常谢谢你,
Jason: Well thanks very much anyway,
不过我担心今晚出去会有问题……你是说免费?
but I'm afraid tonight is out of the quest... I, I, I, did you say free?
迈克:对的.就像小鸟在潘加伯上自由地飞翔.
Mike: Oh yes. As free as the birds that fly over the clouds in Punjab.
杰森:免费?
Jason: Well free, hu?
迈克:是的.你们八点钟能来吗?
Mike: Oh yes. Would eight o' clock be pleasing for you?
杰森:八点可以.好的.
Jason: Eight would be fine. Yes.
迈克:哦,太好了.
Mike: Oh goody. I will be counting the visible minutes.
我会计算时间,到那时再见.
Until then I bid you...adios.
杰森:好,再见.嘿,你想知道什么?嘿,开萝尔,你愿意……
Jason: Ok, bye bye. Hey what do you know? Hey Carol, would you mind uh...
本:看孩子?她很乐意.
Ben: Babysitting? She's love to.
开萝尔:是的,爸爸.我有安排,但是我想我可以.
Carol: Sure dad. I had plans, but I guess I could.
杰森:太好了!换衣服,亲爱的,我请你去吃一顿大餐.
Jason: Great! Get dressed honey, I'm treating you to a fine dinner.
本:迈克,妈妈和爸爸什么时候离开?
Ben: Mike, when are mum and dad going to leave? Hu hu hu?
迈克:本!搞定了!
Mike: Ben! Heal!
开萝尔:好,
Carol: Ok, refreshments are in the back of Mike's car.
茶点在迈克的车上,装饰品藏在走廊上,
The decorations are hidden under the porch,
我甚至没忘了买调味品.
I even remembered to get condiments.
迈克:开萝尔,你在想什么?
Mike: Carol, what are you thinking? These are Junior high School kids.
开萝尔:我还给饭店留了四十元.
Carol: And I dropped forty dollars off at the restaurant.
迈克:四十元是不是太多了?
Mike: Are you sure forty is going to be enough?
开萝尔:那是我在你的衣服所能找到的全部.
Carol: Well it will have to be. That's all I found on your dresser.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
开萝尔:你说你会竭尽全力的,才花了你四十元.
Carol: You said whatever it takes. Well it took your forty bucks.
迈克:我已经花钱雇乐队了.
Mike: Well I already paid for the band.
开萝尔:乐队.什么乐队?
Carol: Band. What band?
(电话铃声)
(phone rings)
开萝尔:对不起.你好,是的,
Carol: Excuse me. Hello. Oh yes Doctor Seaver's here. Um, hold on.
这里是西维尔医生,等一下,同学的父母.
Another parent.
迈克:你好,这里是西维尔医生,请叫我杰森.
Mike: Hello. Yes, this is doctor Seaver. Please, call me Jason.
是的,我会照看这些孩子们,
Yes, I'll keep my eye on the little tykes. I'll be here all evening.
我整晚都在这.好的,拜拜.
Ok, bye bye.
杰森:你星期五整晚都在?
Jason: You'll be here all evening on a Friday night?
你嗓子怎么了?
Is anything wrong with your voice?
迈克:哦,我感冒了,爸爸.这就是我为什么整晚待在家里的原因.
Mike: Oh, yeah I got a cold dad. That's why I'm staying in all night.
嘿,不能传染给长岛的女生们,嘿,爸爸.
Hey, why infect the college women of Long Island? Hey dad.
开萝尔:爸爸,你们再不走,就晚了.
Carol: Dad, aren't you going to be late if you don't leave now?
杰森:我半小时前就准备好了,但是你知道你妈妈是什么样的,
Jason: I was ready half an hour ago, but you now what your mother is like.
她很漂亮,聪明,很有幽默感.
She's gorgeous and smart, and has a great sense of humor.
麦琪:你过奖了,杰森.
Maggie: You're pushing it Jason.
杰森:她在这儿.
Jason: There she is.
麦琪:克莉丝该睡了.
Maggie: Chrissy should sleep through.
迈克和开萝尔:好的,你们玩得开心.
Mike and Carol: Ok, you guys have fun.
杰森:斯汀奇!你们在这儿干什么?
Jason: Stinky! What are you going here?
斯汀奇:你的意思是,我……只是顺便问候一下本.
Stinky: What do you mean what am I....Just dropped in to say hi to Ben.
杰森:穿着礼服?
Jason: Wearing a tuxedo?
斯汀奇:是的,我要去参加我叔叔的葬礼.
Stinky: Well I'm going to my uncle's funeral.
麦琪:带着礼物.
Maggie: With a present.
斯汀奇:我们是马戏团的小丑.
Stinky: We're circus people.
麦琪:晚安.
Maggie: Night.
迈克:好的,晚安.玩得开心点,
Mike: Ok, good night. Have fun. You kids have fun. See you later.
祝你们愉快,再见.我们是马戏团小丑.
We are circus people!
本:茱迪和你们一起来了吗?
Ben: Is Judy with you guys?
斯汀奇:你给本带了什么生日礼物?
Stinky: So, what did you get Ben for his birthday?
维托:今天不是他的生日,傻瓜,我给他一个空盒子.
Vito: It's not his birthday dead head. I got him an empty box.
斯汀奇:那就是我给他的.
Stinky: Ah nuts. That's what I got him.
本:我有口臭吗?
Ben: How's my breath?
维托:放松点,西维尔.一切都很顺利.
Vito: Relax Seaver. This is going to work out fine.
本:好的.
Ben: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
斯汀奇:什么很顺利?
Stinky: What's going to work out fine?
本:这场虚构的聚会给了我一个机会,你们都明白.
Ben: This phony party that I'm having that will give me a chance to, you know.
维托:是的.
Vito: Yeah.
斯汀奇:什么的机会.
Stinky: A chance to what?
维托:接近茱迪.
Vito: Put the movies on Judy.
斯汀奇:为什么?
Stinky: Why?
本:因为.
Ben: Because.
斯汀奇:因为什么?
Stinky: Because what?
本:只是因为.明白吗?
Ben: Just because. Ok?
斯汀奇:你为什么刚才不说呢?
Stinky: Why didn't you just say that in the first place?
本:茱迪在这,她在这.
Ben: Judy's here. She's here.
斯汀奇:我们去和她说.
Stinky: Let's go talk to her.
开萝尔:你约请的乐队在哪呢?
Carol: So where is this band you supposedly got?
迈克:在厨房做准备呢.衣服穿好点.
Mike: In the kitchen getting ready. Keep your shirt on. And I mean that.
我是说那个.我们这有很多小孩子们,容易受影响.
We've got impressionable young children here.
(乐队上场)
(Band comes in)
开萝尔:那是什么?
Carol: What is that?
迈克:那是波纳的叔叔宁佐.他很不错嘛?嘿嘿!
Mike: Its boner's uncle Ninzo. Isn't he great? Hey! Hey! Hey!
本:还要蛋糕吗?
Ben: More cake?
茱迪:三片就够了.
Judy: Three pieces are plenty.
本:你们玩得开心吗?
Ben: Are you having a good time?
茱迪:玩得很开心.
Judy: No. A great time.
本:这是我过的最棒的生日聚会.
Ben: This is the best birthday party I ever had.
茱迪:我还没有祝你生日快乐呢.是吧?
Judy: I haven't even wished you happy birthday yet. Have I.
本:是的,不过已足够了.
Ben: Nah, but that's ok.
茱迪:不,不行.生日快乐,本.
Judy: No, it's not. Happy birthday, Benjamin.
开萝尔:所有人注意了.现在是穿衣服的时间了.
Carol: Ok everybody. Time for the clothe pin drop.
所有人:好!
Everyone: Yeah!
麦琪:哦,杰森,这主意真棒,我梦想的地方.
Maggie: Oh Jason, what a nice idea. What a fancy place.
杰森:什么也比不上我的麦琪.
Jason: Nothing's too good for my Maggie.
麦琪:杰森,我们恢复我们以前一月一次的单独晚餐吧.
Maggie: Jason, let's reestablish our once a month dinner alone rule.
杰森:我想我们已经这样了.
Jason: I think we just did.
侍者:你们好,这里是,
Waiter: Here you are. The Punjab surprise.
哦,我想你会喜欢摩纳哥豆.
Oh and I thought it might please you to enjoy the beans morocco as well.
杰森:摩纳哥豆,我喜欢摩纳哥豆,
Jason: Beans morocco. I love beans morocco.
它是包含在免费晚餐中的?
Is that included in the free dinner as well?
麦琪:免费晚餐?
Maggie: Free dinner?
侍者:当然,
Waiter: Certainly, your check has been, as you say, taken care of.
你的账单上限是40美元.
Up to fifty dollars.
杰森:你们在电话里从来也没提过40美元的上限啊.
Jason: You never mentioned a forty dollar limit on the phone.
侍者:对不起.我还没有这份荣幸,
Waiter: Excuse me. But I have never had the pleasure of speaking to you
能够和你在电话里通话,先生.
on the telephone sir.
杰森:那肯定是老板.
Jason: Ah it must have been the owner.
侍者:我就是这家漂亮饭店的老板,
Waiter: I am the owner of this beautiful establishment.
你不可能和其他人通话.
There is no one else you might have spoken with.
杰森:我开始闻到了一股老鼠味.
Jason: Well, I'm beginning to smell a rat.
开萝尔:安静些!对于这场游戏的胜利者,我们要授予长岛冠军的称号.
Carol: Shhh! To the victor to go the spoils. A close pin drop championship of Long Island.
斯汀奇:谢谢,但是我不叫胜利者.
Stinky: Thanks, but my name's not Victor.
开萝尔:不,斯汀奇,别介意,享受这些.
Carol: No Stinky, see, never mind. Enjoy.
乐师:好,我们现在安静下来,
Musician: Ok, let's slow it down now.
我下面演奏的音乐,大家无法拒绝.
With the music I offer, you can't refuse.
本:你想跳舞吗?
Ben: So, you want to dance?
茱迪:我还担心卢茨欧叔叔不会演奏慢曲呢.
Judy: I was worried that uncle Luccio was never going to play a slow one.
生日快乐.
Happy birthday.
麦琪:这儿在做什么?
Maggie: What is going on here?
杰森:不知道怎么回事.我不放心一个叫斯汀奇的小伙子,
Jason: Somehow, I was not reassured by a kid named Stinky,
他告诉我每件事都很好,然而哈瓦尼格拉却在后面玩.你是谁?
telling me everything was
fine while Havanigella played in the background. Who are you
乐师:我是卢茨欧叔叔.
Musician: I am uncle Nunzio.
杰森:哦.
Jason: Oh.
斯汀奇:哦,我忘了,你爸爸打过电话了.
Stinky: Oh yeah. I forgot. Your dad called.
迈克:好的,开萝尔,
Mike: Da da da da da da da. Alright Carol.
这儿到底发生了什么?
What the heck is going on in here?
麦琪:好的,迈克,还有开萝尔,我只是离开你们留下克莉斯一下,就发生了这些.我希望你们六个月以后不会再有什么计划.
Maggie: Nice try Mike. And Carol, I leave you alone with Chrissy one time, and this is what happens. I hope you don't have any plans for the next six months.
迈克:是的!
Mike: Yeah!
麦琪:你也是,迈克.
Maggie: You either Mike.
开萝尔:妈妈,宝宝很好.
Carol: Mum, the baby's fine.
麦琪:你要原谅我,我得亲自去看一下.
Maggie: Well you'll forgive me if I check for myself.
迈克:爸爸,只是在你我之间,我对开萝尔很失望.
Mike: Dad, just between you and me, I am very very disappointed with Carol.
杰森:(印度腔调)我很高兴听到这些.开萝尔,
Jason: (in Indian accent) Well I am very very happy to hear that.
你马上回你的房间.迈克.
Now Carol, you go to your room right now. And Mike, you go to your apartment.
你去你的.还有本,
And Ben, you and I are going to have a major major talk.
我和你要好好地谈一下.你的朋友们必须回家.
Your friends are going to have to go home.
你也该走了,卢茨欧叔叔.
And that goes for you too, Uncle Nunzio.
维托:一个粗暴的男人.
Vito: Tough break man.
朋友:太糟糕了,他们搅乱了你的生日聚会,本.
Friend: Too bad they have to spoil your birthday like that Bennie.
杰森:生日!
Jason: Birthday!
本:茱迪,我知道你可能会认为我是世界上最大的笨蛋,如果你再也不想和我说话,或者甚至于再次看到我……
Ben: Judy, I know you probably think I'm the biggest weenie in the world, and if you never want to talk to me, or even look at me again...
茱迪:你怎么了?一个为了邀请我参加聚会,陷入麻烦的人是多么的棒.生日快乐,本.
Judy: Are you nuts? Anybody who'd get into this much trouble just to invite me to a party is pretty cool. Happy birthday Benjamin.
本:今天真的不是我的生日.
Ben: It's not really my birthday.
茱迪:别管它.
Judy: Who cares?
迈克:哦!
Mike: Sh!
本:啊!
Ben: Ah!
迈克:我只是想确认你一切安好.
Mike: Sh! I just wanted to make sure that you are ok.
本:好的,我还得上楼见爸爸妈妈,并且……
Ben: Well, I still got to go up and see mum and dad, and...
迈克和本:"欣赏音乐"
Mike and Ben together: "Face the music".
迈克:我知道.
Mike: I know.
本:但是迈克,
Ben: But Mike, it's funny.
那很有趣.我可能要永远关禁闭了,
I'm probably going to be grounded for the rest of my life,
但是那也很值.
but it was worth it.
迈克:什么值?
Mike: What was?
本:迈克,她吻了我.
Ben: Mike, she kissed me.
迈克:嘿,太好了,本.欢迎回到俱乐部.
Mike: Hey, alright Bennie. Welcome to the club.
本:谢谢,这样只会变得更好,是吧?迈克:不,
Ben: Thanks, it only gets better from here. Right?
现在你懂得了真正的痛苦.00:22:23,700
Mike: No, now you learn what real pain is.